After a while, you have to secod the charges.
Fire!
Unit Two!
Good! Stay primed! The fourth wave is coming!
Enemy aircraft have already infiltrated the Southwest region. If they manage to break through here too, Shinjuku is lost.
But we're not gonna let them do that!
They've underestimated our will. No one gets past us.
Here I come!
This region looks like the second wave max không to take!
It's okay tobe!
We're just watching the stream of access to the southeast...
We're just showed US.
We're watching the وال那種.
We're watching the Flash ofставля regulations, and we're not ...
Have a nice video.
That's full of batteries!
Oh wow, am I good or what? This wall is trashed. You shouldn't act so cocky, Lackas. You were ten feet to the right of the target. And yet all the livestock are still dead.
I'll come and get you, I'm always ready to fight. So don't take all of the blame, we're always wet. Always don't take all of the weight, you always do. There will always be something you cannot control. We will overcome, your salvation has begun.
No sun, no light, such a mess all over. Don't kill your wolves, you make me realize who I need.
I'll be there, hold on, the changes somehow, so where are you now? I'll reach you, my dog, the shadows of the earth can lose your support.
The golden end is so wrong, but I know it is a pain that makes us too human after all.
Torn and baby in full of control, about your precious worth. Discarve, may respond to the call.
We've been hit! What? Where? The Whistler Wall!
Chijuku is the Demon Army's second biggest city. How come we'd let the vampires pass by their princes?
Where are the vampire extermination units?
What's going on?
Didn't you hear what they said? The vampires are attacking.
Holy shit. This place has turned into a war zone.
The lieutenant colonel warned us about this. Vampires from the Kansai region are trying to annihilate our military operations.
Are those curse gear the same as my bow?
No, they're not nearly as powerful.
They're simplified versions of your weapons. They're called enchanted gear instead.
Look!
Move!
Incoming! Prepare for battle!
Come on, we gotta help them out!
Move!
Hey, Toishi! Take down that chopper!
Go!
We're clear over here.
We really appreciate your help. That was intense. I'm with Shinjuku Security Unit. Well, the third platoon to be exact. Corporal Nagai. And you must be a vampire extermination unit, right?
Moon Demon Company.
Whoa, you gotta be kidding. I guess our luck hasn't run out yet. Men, ready a transport for these soldiers.
Sir!
The vampires managed to blow a hole in the western defensive barrier just before you showed up. We've got a counter attack squad holding them off right now, but who knows how long they'll last.
Our tactical situation is much worse than I expected.
Yes. It's been a nightmare from the start. Could your group head west and reinforce our defenses? The added support would be a big help.
We don't have to convince us. That's the whole reason we're here.
I guess you're right.
Corporal Nagai. The vehicle is prepped and it is ready to go.
I'll take them as close as I can to the western defense. Remain on high alert.
All right. Let's get moving.
Well, looky here. It's already started. The vampires aren't pulling any punches.
Now, which one of them is the commander?
What? You've got to be kidding. He can see me from that far away?
Um, Lieutenant Colonel Gurren, you don't seem to be too concerned about this fight.
It's not like I'm just slacking off up here, Sayuri.
I'm keeping tabs on the vampire commander and enemy troop movements in case the bastards decide to target this outpost as well.
Damn, I should have known. Speaking of the devils, watch out.
Took you long enough, Mito.
Are you saying I'm late? You're the one who called me here on such short notice. So what's with the big hurry?
Gurren, sir. We've returned from our mission.
It looks like things are going to hell fast. What do you propose we do about it?
There's no way the extermination squad can defeat so many of them, can they?
Great. The whole squad's finally here. Shigure, how's Yu's team doing?
They managed to free all of the civilians. They've moved on to Shinjuku.
Really? Well done. They'll be a good addition to the reinforcement team.
The battlefield is the best place to grow stronger, as long as you don't end up dead.
Okay. It's time we join this fight.
Pretty sure I know where to find the vampire commander. This might be over fast if we take the leader's head.
What's this? Someone's got their eyes on us. Who is it?
Never mind. Nothing for you to worry about. So how are you feeling? It's been a while since you were last here.
You probably have some bad memories of this place, but even I must admit that the humans built themselves a pretty impressive city.
Plus, you may even get a chance to see your beloved you while you're here. What a bonus.
You're going to drink his blood, aren't you, Mika? Go ahead.
You should take advantage of being on the battlefield, since it's forbidden to drink directly from a human back home.
Ha! And why should I follow those rules? They didn't stop you from drinking my blood. You didn't hesitate.
Ha! Don't say such things or you'll hurt my reputation. Besides, it was you who came and offered me your blood that night.
Though, it was so you could steal a gun and map from my mansion. How did that work out for you?
I had no idea that I was playing into your hands or that my family would be killed to amuse you.
How many humans have been slaughtered just because you got a little bored?
Oh, Mika, why are you still upset about ancient history? What's it matter? You're a vampire yourself now.
I'm not upset. At least not at you. I'm angry with myself because I didn't have the power to protect my family.
Hmph. You're a glutton for self-punishment. So, how are you going to protect you? He's the last of your family in this whole wide world.
That's love. It could be eternal. But seriously, Mika, you really need to drink a human's blood soon.
You know what happens to vampires who get too thirsty. I'd hate for that to happen to you.
Mother?
Man, making me think this way.
Let's just go to the gates of a parfait system.
Come on, Mika. Just drink his blood.
Accept that this is your life now, and I promise you, you'll start feeling better.
You'll finally be transformed into a complete vampire with an immortal body and strength far beyond that of a human.
No. No way. I refuse to become a vampire.
You say that now, but your body must be craving blood.
I bet every muscle you have is in pain, thirsty, and crying out for a sip.
Why do you fight it? Give your body what it desires.
Shut up!
You're going to waste a wane.
I'd rather die as a human than live as a vampire!
I see. I'll admit immortality isn't as glamorous as one might think.
It can be boring living for thousands of years, never aging. Maybe you've got the right idea.
There's just one problem. You can't die normally anymore.
Because I've changed you for good. If you don't drink blood, you'll become a hideous demon.
You'll have no will or mind of your own, so you have to drink Mika, or else you'll...
There's no way I'll do it. Never. I will never become a monster like you!
Well, I'll give you another option then.
Drink your fill of my blight. It's the only other way that you'll survive.
There's absolutely no reason for you to refuse this.
Here. Have a little taste.
No. Weren't you listening to me? I won't never become one of you!
That's it. Drink deep.
You're mine now, Mika. You're never going to be able to leave me.
For all eternity. You're my pet. My obedient little blonde servant.
Mikaela Hyakuya.
I've got ten days' worth of Krul's blood.
I have to find you before I run out. Before I'm too thirsty.
We should be at the defensive line in the next 15 minutes. Things might get a little bumpy.
There's something we need to go over before we get to the front line. Listen up!
Huh? What is it?
This might sound weird, but I've got something for you. It's time for you boys to take your medicine.
Wait. What medicine?
Are you in charge of handing out vitamins now?
Remember how strong that noble was?
Surely you'd realize that he was way out of our need.
Even with the Black Demon series weapons, he could have slaughtered us in the blink of an eye.
There'd be nothing left of you.
You will be of no use to the army if you're a bunch of corpses.
Honestly, you'd be as useless as little babies with toys if we were really fighting a noble.
Why is she smiling?
You're not very reassuring. So, what do you want us to do?
Well, this is gonna seem strange, but I'm sure you'll get the hang of it quickly.
Then it'll be second nature.
Here we are.
A pill?
It's how everybody gets a little boost before battle.
Yep. I hate to say it, but we're all doping.
It will help in synchronizing with your demon, and that means your power increases.
So, if I take one of those, I'll be able to kill nobles?
It's not guaranteed, but you'd have a much better chance of not dying.
One pill and you're one and a half times stronger.
If you take two, you're 1.8 times stronger.
That's crazy! Then if I take like ten of them...
You'd probably become some sort of god!
Give me all of them!
One thing, though. Your organs explode when you take three.
Even two pills will severely damage your body and could cause you to die of shock.
To be safe, you should stick to one at first.
Also, the effects only last for 15 minutes.
After the pill wears off, you'll be just as vulnerable as you are now.
Here. A pack for each of you.
Why didn't you give these to us earlier?
We could have used them against that noble.
We could have destroyed that guy.
We still wouldn't have won.
It takes ten seconds before the pill's effects start to take hold.
In those ten seconds, we'd be dead.
He could have killed every single one of us.
One more question.
You mentioned demons earlier.
I definitely want to max out my Black Demon series.
If I take this pill, will I be able to draw out the true power of my cursed gear?
Sorry, the pill is just temporary.
You'll have to study and train more to master the cursed power, but we don't have time for that right now.
Nope. This is war. So for now, you'll take a shortcut.
We need every advantage over the enemy we can get.
You've got a good point.
We could die out there today.
Your class is always half empty, huh?
Hey! I'm just being a realist.
Incoming! We've got to move!
Corporal!
Be careful!
If you get in this place, you'll catch them!
oudouza kabir grains
Bret Whitel
F accomp Socius
K episodic
Get off of it.
Fabulou Bakourine
Fabulou dol ます
Incoming!
Arads
argued
Fabulou
Furus
Dev Plague
Fabulou
Shinoa, hey, come on, wake up.
We fell through to the subway.
Yeah.
Where are the others?
I don't think they fell with us, but the corporal here has banged up pretty badly.
We need to get him to the temporary shelter above ground.
There should be medics there who can treat his wounds.
Hey, idiot!
Down there?
I can hear you.
You okay?
Yeah, of course we are.
There's no way we die in a place like this, dumbass.
Hey, can you guys get out?
Yeah, no problem.
Then you guys go ahead and we'll catch up with you.
We've got to find a med team for the corporal.
We'll meet you at the defensive line.
Wait, shouldn't we...
Kay, see you at the line.
Okay.
We'll be right back.
Hang on.
Bye.
All right.
Ok there you go.
along with me.
I need your blood, you'll read love tonight, I've got great light.
I need your blood, you'll read love tonight, I'll read love tonight, I'll read love tonight, I'll read love tonight.
I need your blood, you'll read love tonight, I'll read love tonight.
I need your blood, you'll read love tonight.
Next time on Seraph of the Ed, results of the choice.